（サイ）鉄の国に入ったら
ナルト君の探索　お願いしますよ。
When we enter the Land of Iron,
please find Naruto, Kiba.
キバ。
（キバ）わかってんよ！
I know!
はぁ…。
（リー）どうしたんです？
What's wrong?
いのは
泣いてるだけだったってのに→
All Ino could do was cry.
サクラは　この覚悟だ。
But look at Sakura's determination.
ナルトに　なんて切り出すのか
知らねえが→
I don't know what she'll say to Naruto,
気まずい雰囲気になるのは
間違いねえからよ。
but it's gonna get
really uncomfortable.
サクラさんも　いろいろ考えが
あるんだと思います。
I'm sure Sakura's got some ideas.
しかし
フォーマンセルが基本だからって→
Four-man squads are the standard,
but any search mission
usually includes me.
探索任務は俺だもんよ。
それに　秘密裏にってのが
サイの注文。
Plus, I've got that secret request
from Sai.
ダンゾウ直轄の暗部…。
I need to use my nose
to see if the Foundation,
根の尾行確認まで
俺の鼻まかせだぜ。
the Anbu under Danzo, is following us.
まったく　鼻使いの荒いやつだぜ。
なぁ　赤丸。
Talk about working us to the bone.
Ain't that right, Akamaru?
なんてことを
してくれやがったんだ　コラ！
Hey you!
Look at what you’ve done!
これだから忍は！
（ヤマト）す　すみません。
That's why I hate ninja.
I-I'm sorry. I'll make sure it's repaired.
私が　ちゃんと
直しておきますから。
Sasuke has shouldered
the entire burden
((マダラ：サスケは　うちはの憎しみを
すべて背負い→
of the Uchiha’s hatred and intends
to strike the world with that curse.
その憎しみの呪いを
世界へ　ぶつけるつもりだ。
最も強い武器であり
友であり　力である憎しみ。
It is the most powerful weapon.
It’s his friend and source of power,
this thing called hatred.
それが　サスケの忍道だ。
And it is Sasuke’s Ninja Way!
(サスケ自身が　そう選択したのさ))
Sasuke chose this himself.
The only thing left to do
is to ask him myself.
（ナルト）もう
直接　会ってみるしかねえんだ。
（エー）シーの見たとおり
火影は　やはり逃げたようだな。
It seems Shee was right.
The Hokage did make an escape.
（オオノキ）ああ　サスケのせいでな。
Yes, because of Sasuke.
暁の計画など
どうせ　ろくなもんではない！
Nothing planned by the Akatsuki
is going to be good.
Who knows what you're up to?
理解できん！
《香燐：サスケが！》
Sasuke is…
サスケを戻せ！
だったら俺の説明を聞け。
Bring Sasuke back!
Then listen to my explanation.
It will all depend on your answer.
その返答次第だ。
Calm down, Raikage.
少し落ち着け　雷影。
聞くだけ聞いて　それからじゃぜ。
Let's hear him out,
and take it from there.
サスケを回復させておけ。
キャ～！
Revive Sasuke.
（カンクロウ）あれが
マダラの能力ってやつか。
So that's Madara's ability?
The Transportation Technique.
（テマリ）時空間忍術だな。
ここは？
Where am I?
さて　そろそろ聞く気に
なってくれたかな？　諸君。
Now then, are you all ready to listen?
（我愛羅）なぜ　お前が
サスケを手なずけようとする？
Why are you trying to win Sasuke over?
須佐能乎まで開眼する
写輪眼は稀だ。
A Sharingan capable of awakening
the Susano'o is rare.
いい眼を
ストックしておきたくなってな。
I like to stock up on good eyes.
五影との実戦で　更に
瞳力を鍛えさせておきたかった。
By battling the Five Kage,
I wanted him to hone
his ocular powers even more.
ここに　サスケを送り込んだのは俺だ。
I'm the one who sent Sasuke here.
五影を弱らせて
人質に取ろうと思っていた。
I was intending on weakening the Five Kage
and taking you all hostage.
そこまでは
まだ無理だったようだが。
It seems that is still not possible.
（メイ）人質？　何のために？
Taking us hostage?
For what purpose?!
さっき言った
月の眼計画を円滑に運ぶためだ。
To smoothly implement
the aforementioned Project Tsuki no Me.
本当に　あのうちはマダラが
生きていたとは驚きじゃが。
It's quite shocking to learn that
Madara Uchiha is still alive,
お前ほどの男が　なぜ
こんな回りくどいやり方をする？
but why would a man of your skill
resort to such a roundabout method?
お前の力なら　どんな計画でも
思いどおりのはずじゃぜ。
Surely, you have the strength
to bring any plan to fruition.
初代火影柱間との戦いの傷が
深すぎたのだ。
The injuries I sustained during my battle
with the First Hokage Hashirama
were too severe.
今の俺には　力は無い。
I have no strength in me now.
いわば　ただの
形骸化した存在に過ぎない。
You could say I am merely
a shell of my old self.
（シー）お前が本来の自分に
戻るための計画ってやつか。
Is this a plan to restore yourself?
うむ　そうとも言えるが…。
You could say that.
But that's not all.
ただ　それだけではない。
（ミフネ）何をたくらむ？
月の眼計画とは　いったい何だ！
What are you scheming?!
Just what is this Project Tsuki no Me?!
I want to take my time talking to you.
Let me sit down.
ゆっくり話したい。
腰を下ろさせてもらう。
We’re asking you
what kind of plan it is!
どんな計画かって
聞いてんだろうが！
すべてが　俺とひとつになる。
All shall become one with me,
and result in a complete
possession form that unites all.
すべての統一をなす完全体だ。
Become one? Unite all?
ひとつになる…
すべての統一じゃと？
どういうことじゃ！
What do you mean?!
うちはには
代々　伝わる石碑がある。
The Uchiha have
an ancient stone tablet
that has been passed down
through the generations.
今も木ノ葉の地下に存在する。
It still exists underground in
the Hidden Leaf Village.
そこには　かつての六道仙人が
書きつけた秘密が記してある。
Upon it are written secrets,
engraved by the Sage of
the Six Paths himself.
It cannot be read unless
you possess ocular powers.
瞳力がなければ
読むことができず→
With the Sharingan,
写輪眼　万華鏡写輪眼
輪廻眼の順に→
the Mangekyo Sharingan
and Rinnegan, in that order,
the contents become
increasingly visible.
解読できる内容が増える。
話が眉唾ものになってきたな。
Your story is unlikely.
The Sage of the Six Paths doesn't…
六道仙人など。
It is the truth!
これは事実だ。　彼は存在した。
He did exist.
And he left the stone tablet.
そして　石碑を残した。
Don't change the subject!
話がそれた。
What does your plan have to do
with the Sage of the Six Paths?!
お前の計画と　その六道仙人と
何の関係がある？
なぜ　彼が伝説となり→
Do you know why he became
a legendary figure
and a godlike figure
that is revered as a god of ninja?
忍の神のように崇められるように
なったのか知っているか？
そこに俺の目的と
この男とのつながりがある。
There lies the link between my plan
and this man.
Madara Uchiha…
うちはマダラ…　あなたは
万華鏡写輪眼をもち→
You possess the Mangekyo Sharingan
and among the Akatsuki,
暁には　輪廻眼のやからもいた。
there was one who possessed
the Rinnegan.
You know everything, don't you?
あなたも
すべてを知っているのね。
聞こう。
We're listening.
He once saved the world
from a certain monster.
彼は　かつて世界を救った。
ある化け物から。
化け物？
Monster?
我愛羅　お前もその化け物の一部が
封印されていたにすぎない。
Gaara, you also had one part of
that monster sealed inside you.
そいつは　尾獣すべての集合体。
最強のチャクラをもつ存在。
That monster was the combination of
every Tailed Beast in existence.
Something that possessed
the most powerful chakra.
The Ten-Tails!
十尾だ。
Declaration of War
そいつは　尾獣すべての集合体。
最強のチャクラをもつ存在。　十尾だ。
That monster was the combination
of every Tailed Beast in existence.
Something that possessed
the most powerful chakra.
The Ten-Tails.
尾獣は　九尾までじゃないのか！？
Aren't there only nine Tailed Beasts?!
言ったはずだ。　そいつは
尾獣すべての集合体だと。
I just told you.
It was the combination of
all the Tailed Beasts.
守鶴…　我愛羅の尾獣の…。
Shukaku, Gaara's Tailed Beast
known as…
一尾。
the One-Tail!
The fiery Monster Cat of
the Hidden Cloud's Yugito Ni’i…
炎の怪猫　雲隠れの二位ユギトの…。
二尾。
the Two-Tails!
先代　水影の…。
The former Mizukage's…
三尾。
Three-Tails!
熔遁の老紫が四尾。
Roshi of the Lava Style’s…
Four-Tails!
岩隠れのハンの五尾。
Han of the Hidden Stone’s…
Five-Tails!
抜け忍　ウタカタの六尾。
The Rogue Ninja Utakata’s…
Six-Tails!
滝隠れ　フウの七尾。
Fuu of the Hidden Waterfalls’…
Seven-Tails!
雷影の弟　キラービーの八尾。
Raikage's younger brother,
Killer Bee’s…
Eight-Tails!
そして　木ノ葉の妖狐　九尾。
And the fox spirit of the Hidden Leaf…
the Nine-Tails!
一尾から九尾の尾獣は→
The Ten-Tails' chakra was simply
divided up into the nine Tailed Beasts,
その十尾のチャクラを
分散したものにすぎない。
六道仙人の手によってな。
by the Sage of the Six Paths.
嫌な話の流れじゃん。
I don't like where this story is headed.
だから　暁は
尾獣を集めたってことか。
Is that why the Akatsuki are
gathering the Tailed Beasts?
六道仙人は
十尾から　世界を守るため→
The Sage of the Six Paths
developed a certain ninjutsu
ある忍術を開発した。
in order to protect the world
from the Ten-Tails.
今も　その忍術は
密かに受け継がれている。
Even today, that ninjutsu is still
being secretly passed down.
人柱力の封印術システム…。
It is the Sealing Jutsu process
for Jinchuriki.
そう。　六道仙人は
十尾の人柱力だった。
Yes, the Sage of the Six Paths was
the Ten-Tails' Jinchuriki.
十尾をおさえこむために
その体に　十尾を封印したのだ。
In order to suppress it,
he sealed the Ten-Tails within his body.
人々を苦しめていた十尾から
世界を救った仙人は→
The Sage, who saved
a world terrorized by the Ten-Tails,
became a savior and won praise as a god.
神のように　崇め奉られた。
しかし　あまりに強大にして
邪悪な十尾のチャクラは→
But if the Sage died, the powerful
and demonic chakra of the Ten-Tails
己が死ねば　封印が解け
また　表へ出てしまう。
would once again be released
unto the world.
それを恐れた　六道仙人は→
Fearing this, at the time of his death,
死に際に　最後の力を使い→
the Sage of the Six Paths summoned
every last ounce of his power
十尾のチャクラを　九つに分散し
各地へと　バラまいた。
to partition the Ten-Tails' chakra
into nine parts
and scattered them across the world.
そして　十尾のチャクラを
抜かれた本体は封印され→
Then he sealed the Ten-Tails' body,
now devoid of chakra,
力の及ばない空へと飛ばされた。
and hurled it into the sky.
それが月となった。
And it became the moon.
（ダルイ）話がでかすぎる。
What a tall tale!
As if a human could do such a thing.
人間に　そんなことが
本当にできるのか？
十尾の人柱力となった六道仙人は
すでに　人外の輩になっていた。
When he became
the Jinchuriki of the Ten-Tails,
the Sage of the Six Paths went
beyond the realm of humans.
お前が　その分散してあった
九つのチャクラ…。
I understand now that
you seek that inhuman power
つまり　すべての尾獣を集めて→
by gathering the chakra of the nine,
namely all, of the Tailed Beasts.
その人外の力を
手にするつもりなのは　わかった。
が…　そんな力
手に入れて　何をする？
But what will you do with all that power?
十尾復活。
Revive the Ten-Tails.
そして俺は　十尾の人柱力となる。
And I will become
the Ten-Tail’s Jinchuriki.
その力を利用し
己の瞳力を強化させ→
I will use its power to strengthen
my ocular powers,
そして　ある術を発動させる。
and activate a certain jutsu.
ある術じゃと？
A certain jutsu?! What is it?
なんじゃ　それは。
何をするつもりじゃ！
What do you intend to do?
月に　己の眼を投影する大幻術。
A Super Genjutsu,
where I project my eyes off the moon.
無限月読。
Infinite Tsukuyomi.
地上に存在する　すべての人間に
幻術をかける。
I will cast a genjutsu on every human
that walks the earth.
And in that genjutsu, I will control
all humans and unify the world.
俺が　すべての人間を
その幻術のなかでコントロールし→
世界をひとつにするのだ。
わだかまりも　争いもない世界だ。
A world without hatred or war.
Everything will become one with me,
everything will be united.
すべてが　俺とひとつになる。
すべての統一。
それが俺の　月の眼計画。
That is my Project Tsuki no Me.
ふざけるな！
お前などに　世界は渡さん！
Stop joking around!
I’m not handing the world over to you!
幻の平和など　ごまかしだ。
Peace that exists only as
an illusion is deception.
Peace is only meaningful when it is
genuinely achieved in the real world.
現実の世界でなしえてこそ
意味がある。
そんなもののなかに
何があるっていうの？
So what exists inside such a world?
There is no hope, no dreams!
It’s just an escape!
希望も夢もない！
逃げているだけよ！
世界をひとつにするか…。
Unite the world, huh?
たしか　ダンゾウも
同じようなことを言っとったが→
Danzo mentioned something similar.
お前のは
世界をひとつにするというより→
But instead of uniting the world,
世界を自分ひとりのものに
したいとしか聞こえん。
it just sounds like you want to
make the world yours!
フフフ…。
All this talk and yet,
what have you Five Kage accomplished?
そういう　お前たち五影に
何ができたというのだ？
お前たちなら
本当は理解しているはずだ。
You of all people should know by now…
希望など　ないことを。
There is no such thing as hope!
希望とは
あきらめに等しいものだ。
To hope is equivalent to giving up,
and it’s the biggest deception of all.
それこそ
ごまかしのセリフでしかない。
残りの八尾と九尾を差し出し→
Turn over the remaining
Eight-Tails and Nine-Tails,
and cooperate with my plan.
俺の計画に　もろもろ協力しろ。
Or there will be war.
でなければ　戦争になる。
戦争だと？
八尾？
War you say?
The Eight-Tails?
What are you talking about?
どういうことだ！？
ビーは　お前たちが…。
Didn't you get Bee?
八尾の捕獲には失敗し
逃げられた。
The attempt to capture
the Eight-Tails failed and he escaped.
He is a ninja who is a perfect Jinchuriki.
あれこそ　人柱力として
完璧な忍だ。
お前の弟だけある。
Only your younger brother
has got what it takes.
はぁっ！？
Huh?!
あぁ…　やっぱり
そんな気もしてたんすよね。
Yeah, I sort of had a feeling about that.
はぁ…。
That idiot!
あの　アホーンめ！
He used that chance to slip away and now,
he's having the time of his life!
これを機に
里の外へ出て　遊んどるのか！
Unforgivable!
He's going to get my Iron Claw!
許さ～ん！　アイアンクローじゃ！
うずまきナルトは渡さない。
We will not hand over Naruto Uzumaki.
I agree with him!
私も同じく。
雷影　お前は？
What about you, Raikage?
There's no way I'll let him have
my younger brother!
もちろん　弟は渡さん！
俺には　力はないが
今までに集めた尾獣の力がある。
I don't have the strength,
but the Tailed Beasts
we've gathered so far, do.
You people have no chance of winning.
お前たちに勝ち目はないぞ。
We haven't given up hope.
希望は捨てない。
Very well.
いいだろう。
第四次忍界大戦。
ここに宣戦を布告する。
I hereby declare the start
of the Fourth Great Ninja War.
第四次忍界大戦じゃと？　正気か？
The Fourth Great Ninja War?
Are you mad?!
The next time we meet will be
on the battlefield.
今度は　戦場で会おう。
さて　どうしたもんかのう。
Well then, what do we do now?
忍連合軍を作るしかない。
We have to form
an Allied Shinobi Force.
七体もの尾獣の力に
対抗するにはな。
It’s the only way we can counter
the power of the seven Tailed Beasts.
雷影様は反対してましたが？
You were opposed to this,
weren't you, Lord Raikage?
弟は無事だったようだが→
It seems my younger brother is alive.
We cannot allow ourselves to be
manipulated by the Akatsuki any longer.
これ以上　暁に　だらだらと
振り回されるわけにはいかん。
連合軍を作り　一気にケリをつける。
Form the alliance and
settle this once and for all!
木ノ葉はどうするんじゃ？
What about the Hidden Leaf?
The Hokage ran off.
火影が逃げたままじゃぜ。
ダンゾウは　黒い噂が絶えん。
There is too much suspicion
surrounding Danzo.
今回の会談の件で
わしらの信用を失った。
He lost our trust at this summit.
それに　これが
木ノ葉の忍たちに知られれば→
When the Hidden Leaf ninja
learn about him,
木ノ葉での　ダンゾウの立場も危うい。
いずれ失脚だ。
his position in the village will
become insecure.
He will be removed in no time!
忍連合軍の話は　俺が信用できる
木ノ葉の忍に伝えておく。
I will speak to someone I trust among
the Hidden Leaf
regarding the Allied Shinobi Force.
誰だ？
写輪眼の　はたけカカシだ。
Who would that be?
Kakashi Hatake of the Sharingan.
あの白い牙の息子か？
You mean the White Fang’s son?
((カカシ：今ここで　若い忍が
不器用なりに　雲と木ノ葉…。
Right here and now, this young ninja,
no matter how awkwardly,
is bowing his head in his affection
互いの国　里を思い
頭を下げている。
for the Cloud and Leaf,
village and nation.
雷影様
あなたは五影のひとりとして→
Lord Raikage…
As one of the five Kage,
what do you think of this?
(これを
どうとらえ　どう思われる？))
いいだろう。
ダンゾウよりは信用できそうだ。
Fine. He seems more trustworthy
than Danzo.
だな。
Agreed.
雷影様　すぐにでも
キラービーを捜す手配をつけましょう。
Lord Raikage, we must take measures
to find Killer Bee immediately!
暁が
八尾と九尾を狙っているなら→
If the Akatsuki want
the Eight-Tails and Nine-Tails,
やつらも　まだ　ビーを
執拗に追っているはずです。
they are probably still pursuing Bee.
うむ。
シー　すぐに捜索隊を編成して→
Yes. Shee, send word to
the village to put together
a Tracking Unit to begin the search
for Bee immediately!
ビーを捜させるよう
里に連絡しておけ。
はっ。
Yes sir!
We must notify Samui's team too.
サムイ小隊にも
すぐに知らせてやんなきゃな。
オモイもカルイも落ち込んでたからさ。
Omoi and Karui have been
feeling quite distraught.
マダラの　月の眼計画とやらを
阻止するために→
If we are to stop
Madara's Project Tsuki no Me,
we cannot let the Eight-Tails and
Nine-Tails fall into his hands.
絶対に
八尾と九尾を渡しては駄目です。
だから　八尾と九尾を
こちらの連合軍で→
I think it is imperative that
our Allied Shinobi Forces find the two first
先に見つけ出して　隠しておくのが
ベストだと思われますが。
and place them into hiding.
（長十郎）そ…　そのとおりです！
Y-You're absolutely right!
If the day comes when
this Ten-Tails is revived…
もし　十尾とかが
復活なんかした日には…。
いや　マダラの持つ
七体の尾獣が集まった力は→
However, we cannot even imagine
the power Madara wields
with the seven Tailed Beasts
he already has.
想像もできん。
それに　尾獣を使った術や
隠し球を持っとるやもしれんぜ。
Furthermore, he may possess
certain jutsu or a trump card
for using the Tailed Beasts.
（赤ツチ）でなきゃ
あんな強気には出てこんだに。
Otherwise, he wouldn't have
come on so strong.
わしら　忍連合軍側にも
八尾と九尾の尾獣は→
Perhaps it would be wise for
the Allied Shinobi Forces to plan
on using the Eight-Tails and Nine-Tails
as military weapons too.
戦力として計算したほうが
いいのではないか？
それは駄目だ。
That cannot happen.
これは　２人を守る戦争でもある。
This is also a war to protect those two.
There is a reason why Madara
is waging war
マダラが集めた七体の尾獣で
戦争を仕掛ける理由…。
with just the seven Tailed Beasts
he has collected thus far.
おそらく　弱っている今のマダラや
暁メンバーだけでは→
It is too difficult for Madara,
in his weakened state,
and the Akatsuki members to capture
the Eight-Tails and Nine-Tails.
八尾と九尾を
捕らえることが難しいからだ。
できたとしても
リスクが大きすぎると考えた。
And even if they had succeeded,
he felt the risk was too great.
それに　戦争で
２人を誘い出すためかもしれない。
That is why he may be hoping to
lure the two to his side through war.
In any case, using the Eight-Tails
and Nine-Tails for battle
いずれにせよ　八尾と九尾を
戦争に駆り出すのは→
is not a wise strategy.
得策とはいえない。
私も　それがいいと考えます。
I agree.
わしも風影の意に同意だ。
I also concur with the Kazekage.
もしものことを考えれば
敵の前に　八尾と九尾を→
If we consider
the worst-case scenario,
it will be like offering the Eight-Tails
or Nine-Tails on a silver platter!
おいそれと出すわけにはいかん。
そもそも
八尾である　わしの弟は→
And besides, the Eight-Tails is
my younger brother and
作戦などという言葉には
縁遠いやつだ。
"military strategy" is
a foreign concept to him.
何をしでかすか　わからん。
I can’t predict what he’d do.
イェ～イ！
Yay!
逆に　戦場が
混乱するかもしれんしな。
He may just create more chaos
on the battlefield!
九尾のナルトも同じだ。
Naruto the Nine-Tails,
would do the same.
言えてるじゃん。
だな。
– That's for sure.
– I'll say.
わかりました。
では　八尾と九尾は→
I understand.
Well then, Lord Tsuchikage,
保護拘束ということで
どうです？　土影様。
our aim will be to protect and
confine the Eight-Tails and Nine-Tails.
うむ。
岩　霧　砂　木ノ葉には→
Fine.
Intel about Killer Bee
will be provided to
the Stone, Mist, Sand and Leaf Villages.
キラービー情報を提供する。
Use it to form Tracking Units
and get moving!
それを　もとに捜索チームを編成し
すぐに動け！
八尾は　見つけ次第→
Send word the instant
you find the Eight-Tails.
わしのところへ
連絡がくるようにしろ。
My younger brother will
only heed orders from me!
弟は　わしの
言うことぐらいしか聞かん！
それと風影…。
さっきのカカシへの件　頼むぞ。
By the way, Kazekage, we will leave
the matter with Kakashi to you.
ああ。
Yes.
On my way here,
ここに来る道中で
はたけカカシと→
I met Kakashi Hatake and
the boy who is the Nine-Tails' Jinchuriki.
九尾の人柱力のガキに会った。
まだ　この鉄の国に
いるかもしれん。
They might still be here
in the Land of Iron.
You should start your search
for them here.
まずは　この国から捜してみろ。
了解した。
Understood.
あ…　あの…
ちょっと　いいですか？
U-Um… May I say something?
なんだ？
あ…　はい。
What is it?
Uh… Yes… Umm…
あの…　その…。
さっさと話せ！
Spit it out!
あ…　暁には
まだ　僕と同じ忍刀七人衆の→
I-In the Akatsuki, there's someone who,
like me, is a member of
the Seven Ninja Swordsmen of the Mist.
Kisame Hoshigaki.
干柿鬼鮫がいます。
He has chakra equal to that
of a Jinchuriki
その人は…
人柱力並みのチャクラ量と→
as well as a sword known
as Samehada, Shark Skin,
七人衆の刀のなかでも→
which is the most evil, even among
the Seven Ninja Swordsmen of the Mist.
最悪な鮫肌を持っていて…。
When his chakra and sword merge,
even though he is human,
刀と融合すると
人間でありながら→
he releases power close to
that of a Jinchuriki.
人柱力に近い力を発揮する
尾を持たない尾獣だって…。
He is like a Tailed Beast
without the tail.
先輩たちから　そう聞きました。
That's what I've been told by my seniors.
あいつは特別だって…。
決して　なめないほうが。
He is extraordinary and
must not be underestimated.
そんなことは　わかっとる。
We already know that!
But are you all sure about this plan?
それより…
本当に　それでええのか？
マダラの操るであろう
七体の尾獣の力は未知じゃぜ。
We do not know what kind of power
the seven Tailed Beasts possess
under Madara.
もし　八尾と九尾を拘束して→
If we confine the Eight-Tails
and Nine-Tails,
わしら　忍連合軍が
２人を守ったところで…。
and our Allied Shinobi Force is destroyed
while protecting these Tailed Beasts,
その連合軍が
全滅しては　意味がない。
our entire effort would
have been meaningless.
だったらじゃぜ…
端から　２人を参戦させ→
If that is the case, I think it is better to
use the two right from the beginning
連合軍と
協力戦を仕掛けたほうが→
in a combined effort with
the Allied Shinobi Forces.
有利だと思うがのぅ。
それは　どうかな？
I wonder about that.
今ここに　世界初の忍連合軍が
できつつある。
At this moment, the world's first
Allied Shinobi Force is being formed.
その力も　また未知数…。
Its power is also unknown.
マダラが
七体の尾獣の力を使用するにも→
Madara will also be taking a great risk
in pitting the power of
the seven Tailed Beasts against it.
リスクがあるはずだ。
でなければ　ここへ来て→
Otherwise, why would he have come
to this summit to try to negotiate?
わざわざ交渉を
持ちかけたりはしない。
He must also be dealing with
unfavorable conditions.
むこうにも
不利な条件があるのでござろう。
それに…　この戦争
我々　侍も参戦する！
Furthermore, we Samurai
will also participate in this war!
土影殿…　これでも　まだ
心配事がおありか？
Lord Tsuchikage…
Do you still have doubts even now?
フン！
Looks like the Raikage and
Kazekage went upstairs.
（水月）雷影や風影も
上に行ったようだしさ。
やっぱ　先に行ったんだよ。
サスケも香燐も。
Sasuke and Karin must
have gone ahead.
俺たちも　上に行ってみる？
We should go up too.
（重吾）だが　警戒されている…。
すぐに見つかる。
But it's guarded.
We'll be spotted right away.
ならさ
いい方法があるんだけど…。
Well, I have a good way.
（黒ツチ）なんだったんだ　こいつ…。
What the hell was he?
So gross!
キモイなぁ　もう！
《今までどおり　やってたら→
If we keep doing what
we’ve always done,
サスケ捜しても　見つかりっこねえ。
仙人モード　使うしかねえってばよ。
まずは　持続時間上げねえと！》
ナルト　そろそろ入ってこい！
やっと見つけたぜ！
サクラちゃん。
サイにキバ…　ゲジマユまで。
なんで　お前たち
ここへ来たの？
ナルト…。
あんたに話があるの。
＜１９７０年代　１０年間に生まれた→
演歌・歌謡曲
更に　フォーク＆ロックの名曲を大公開！
インターネット　街頭アンケート→
更に　当時の売り上げをもとに→
ランキングを決定！＞
＜今　青春時代の名曲が
よみがえる！＞